One second.
Quiet, please.
Listen, the most important thing for me in doing this every Monday for the past eight years is to show love to the people that I care about and also to show love to people that I don't know.
Yeah. You know what I'm saying? And to create a space for everybody to be themselves. You know what I'm saying? Present your music and catch your vibe and, you know, no judgment. Can we have the quiet ladies upstairs?
And this space is really for us to show each other love and for us to express ourselves as artists. It's very important for me to be able to do that without having any sort of hindrance on, oh, you got to sound like this or you got to do that.
You know, just do your thing. And so Amanda Seals is just an incredible mind. She's an author. She's a visionary. She's a poet. She's an emcee. She's a vocalist. She's a cutler. Cutler. She's got a cutler. She's got a cutler.
Cut her cut me. You know what I'm saying? She ain't got me to play. Y'all better listen.
And she's my cancerian sister. And it's cancer season.
Pick up on my cancer.
Yes. Show us some love. She's got some incredible music. We made some incredible music together.
Yes, we have.
And we got some more music we're gonna be making together. But show her some love, y'all.
all right y'all so first of all let's make some noise for the brothers up here
who have been doing the goddamn thing gray angry and the council goldfinger i'm gonna tell you now
this this little faint clap shit y'all doing right now is very annoying so i need y'all to
make some noise for the brothers who have been here bringing you all thank you thank you we have
to keep the energy up because the energy is all we got right now all right the energy is all we got
right now we got folks out here that are working every single day to try to mine you of your positive
energy of your resistance energy of your revolutionary energy and so this music right
here is what brings us back to the ground it's what brings us back to each other it's what brings
us back around there's a reason why all indigenous cultures have the drum have the drum because your
body's on and your heart is beating in the same way the earth is beating and right now we got a lot of
motherfuckers that we need to get some music i decided i needed to make movement music so
it's been 15 years since i put out a project this is the first time i ever produced a project so i feel
very honored to be in the present i ended up producing it because this nigga ray angry was
too then i was just you know finagling and finicking around and i was like yo i think i'm nice b
and that's how it happens so tonight i want to bring you all through my latest project truth
translator truth translator is not about me it's about us all of us and the necessity for us to
become truth translators because the lies are being weaponized against us will you all allow me to take
you on this journey will you all allow me to take you so over the course of these records we are going
to be moving our energy through us through the key gong through the fire in our bellies and i want you
to listen to not only me but listen to yourselves oh my god stop there we go okay hold on because you
see this is what happens when when you're new to the shit and you gotta be up here trying to figure
shit out in real time i'm gonna blame it on perimenopause and that's how we're gonna do it
because i can't get this shit to stop um stop make it stop make it stop make it stop make it oh my god
y'all it won't there it is okay thank you let's bring it back the cordless is to clear a path follow
me the sage expels energy wake up your belly y'all the truth and thus we must all be its translators
into your fist let's get our energy going and we are told that we cannot create something better for
ourselves we just watch these musicians up here create something from nothing to keep it a buck they
created everything from nothing let's be real because i know that they restored me and we have the power
within us to restore us this next record is dedicated to us remembering that power and
charting our own course for a better way
busy with people just talking all the motherfucking time but not really igniting people to do anything
you see what happens on the internet is that every time you comment on something that pisses you off
it's a pressure valve release but we need the pressure we need the pressure to actually rise up and do
what we need to do because we're under a psychological operation on a regular basis that convinces us
that someone is going to come save us and i promise you it's never going to happen it's all going to
happen with us so it is imperative that we wake the fuck up another thing is to disseminate propaganda
to influence people's minds and this is a major function of the cava
the bass is going to come in real quick hold on for it hold on i'm from florida so it's always going to show up
because i came from doing stand-up and i'm coming back to music and i'm starting fresh and so you guys are my little
fresh start so so thank you the cancer in me is like let's turn it up like that doesn't include making my chest
this is a keffiyeh this is a keffiyeh representative and from philistine philistine is the arabic
pronunciation of palestine many of you may not think that what is taking place in palestine has
anything to do with you i am here to correct you it has everything to do with you on many levels on
the spiritual level because at the end of the day we're all connected and if they're trying to get rid
somebody they're trying to get rid of you right on a physical level we're connected because all of
the bombs that they're dropping over there end up traveling toxically across this earth through the
water through the soil through the air and back to you and on a political level in the fact that
the soldiers that are over there indiscriminately taking lives are training the police over here to
indiscriminately take lives the money that you're making and that you are paying in taxes is being
used to fund a genocide it's being used to build up an economy of a country that has no interest in
your elevation and growth you don't have health care you don't have free education but they do in
israel so when we talk about palestine we're not talking about a political issue we're talking about
a personal issue that affects you on a multitude of levels and that has affected me on a multitude
of levels and should remind all of us that we need to rise up for all of us
because they showing us how to get free so if you haven't been paying attention they over there
fucking shit up and it's very inspiring before i go i want to remind you all that you have
everything that you need listen to me you have everything that you need within you
to do what we need to do we come in here we enjoy ourselves we receive this music but i want us to
remember this music is not meant to dull us this music is not meant to distract us it's meant to empower
us it's meant to restore us it's meant to revive us there is magic in you that sees magic in me it is how we
will change in truth we will take these devils down with the magic we move there is magic in you
come on y'all that sees magic in me it is how we will change with the magic we move thank y'all
yeah i'm truth translator at amandaseals.com at amandadeepanmusic.com and i want y'all to
remember that art is a vital aspect of revolution and resistance so make sure that as much as you are
liking these influencers who are telling you the information make sure you like these artists who
are singing you who are writing you and who are drawing you the inspiration good night